{
  "module": {
    "number": 1,
    "name": "GeneralKnowledge",
    "questions": 15,
  },
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "You give me blood, I will give you freedom Whose slogan was that?",
      "answers": [
        " Subhash Chandra Bose",
        " Mahatma Gandhi",
        "Shyamlal Gupta Councilor",
        " Savarkar"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Which country started the renaissance in the world?",
      "answers": [
        "Italy",
         "Britain",
        "France",
        "Germany",
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    }
    {
        "number": 3,
        "question": " The Chief Minister of which state has launched a web portal and a mobile application developed by the state finance department named 'Hamar Apan Budget'?",
        "answers": [
            "West Bengal",
            "Jharkhand",
            "Karnataka",
            "Chhattisgarh",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
      }
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "Who has recently become the new Chancellor of Germany?",
        "answers": [
            "dam Charles",
            "Olaf Scholz",
            "Max Diamond",
            "Yuda Diskatche",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
      }
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "Q: Which State has recently launched the Student Police Cadet (SPC) scheme for class 8 and 9 students?",
        "answers": [
          "Madhya Pradesh",
          "Rajasthan",
          "Gujarat"
          "Odisha",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
      }
      {
        "number": 6,
        "question": " How many countries have been declared as COVID-19 free till 9 June?",
        "answers": [
          "4",
          "7",
          "9", 
          "12",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 3
      }
      {
        "number": 7,
        "question": " Which bank is the partner bank of PM-CARES?",
        "answers": [
          "PNB",
          "SBI",
          "RBI",
          "Yes Bank",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
      }
      {
        "number": 8,
        "question": " Which country has recently launched Soyuz Carrier Rocket with 33 Satellites?",
        "answers": [
          "Russia",
          "US",
          "China",
          "Italy",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
      }
      {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "Q: What is the currency of Mexico?",
        "answers": [
          "euro",
          "peso",
          "rand",
          "dinar",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
      }
      {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "Q: 180 m long Train A crosses Train B of 120 m in length which is running in opposite direction in 60/11sec. If speed of train B is 20% more than that of train A, then find the time taken by both trains to cross each other, when they running in same direction?",
        "answers": [
          "60 sec",
          "258 sec",
          "355 sec",
          "450sec",
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
      }
 

  ]
}